are we
Speaker 1: good guys are we rolling
in
Speaker 2: this age of propaganda and the media has done a really good job of creating a caricature of candace owens
what's going to be
Speaker 3: different about
Speaker 3: Candace at The Daily Wire. The timing right now is really crucial to stand up on
Speaker 4: a platform and to say, I'm here, I'm a conservative, I'm not apologizing. I
am really committed
Speaker 4: to changing things. I have the courage to stand by my convictions and genuinely believe in the importance of challenging ideas and the importance of debate. And that's why I'm really excited to join The Daily Wire team. This show is going to be uplifting, funny, political. This show is going to be all of the pieces of me.